[{"question":"# Q1. When developing a backlink strategy, what approach would be most beneficial?","options":["Guest post the article to as many sites as possible","Create an infographics and share it with relevant bloggers","Create diverse and unnatural links","Distribute links in comment sections of websites"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Guest post the article to as many sites as possible"},{"question":"# Q2. What is a key reason the URL `domain.com/apparel/jackets` is preferable to the URL `domain.com/p=141`?","options":["It is longer","It is not preferable","It uses structured markup","It is readable to a human"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"It is readable to a human"},{"question":"# Q3. Which HTTP response status code would indicate a page has been moved permanently?","options":["410","302","200","301"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"301"},{"question":"# Q4. You notice a website is serving HTML to a Search Engine than to a human user. What is this an example of?","options":["Spam injection","Cloaking","Sneaky Redirect","Splicing"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Cloaking"},{"question":"# Q5. What would significantly improve Google&#39;s ability to a non-YouTube video in its Search Results?","options":["Provide a 150 x 80 pixel thumbnail image","Add Schema.org VideoObject","Convert .mp4 videos to .mov","Embed video objects with JavaScript conditionals"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Add Schema.org VideoObject"},{"question":"# Q6. Google primarily determines indexing and ranking by crawling which version of a page?","options":["Responsive version","Submitted version","Mobile version","Desktop version"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Responsive version"},{"question":"# Q7. You want to identify which US state has the most search interest for a particular keyword. What tool would help you determine this?","options":["Google Analytics","Google Keyword Planner","Google Search Console","Google Trends"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Google Trends"},{"question":"# Q8. You want to block crawlers from accessing your entire website. What robots.txt entry would you use?\n- [ ]\n```markdown\nUser-agent: Allbots\nDisallow: \\*\n\n```","options":["- [ ]"]},{"question":"# Q9. Which results is most likely if you use an interstitial pop-up that requires a user to take action before you load the content of the page?","options":["Both the pop-up and the content of the page will be indexed","The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content","An interstitial pop-up is treated the same as a soft 404","The pop-up will be ignored, and the content of the page will be indexed correctly"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"The pop-up will be indexed instead of the desired body content"},{"question":"# Q10. You notice a particular product in an e-commerce storefront is no longer indexed despite no technical issues. What is a likely reason for this?","options":["No title or meta description tags were provided","The Keywords is too competitive","Robots.txt is configured to allow access","The product is out of stock"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"No title or meta description tags were provided"},{"question":"# Q11. All bylone dates for articles are suddenly no longer visible on a `website&#39;s` listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?","options":["The site has been delisted from Google Search","A Google News sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a publisher center account","The site kept updating the dates to make the content appear fres, without changing","The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site"},{"question":"# Q12. Which approach is not advisable to Geo-targeting your website?","options":["Using a gTLD with subdomain","using URL parameters","Using a ccTLD","Using a gTLD with a subdirectory"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"using URL parameters"},{"question":"# Q13. You have been asked to help a big e-commerce brand optimize their website for search engines. They currently have thousands of products listed on their website. What is your most appropriate first step?","options":["Recommend that they add more products","WOrd on compressing image files","302 redirect all product pages to URL that contains target keywords","302 redirect all product ages to a URL that contains target keywords","Register the business with a Google My Business account."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"WOrd on compressing image files"},{"question":"# Q14. What Does The Term &quot;Sandbox&quot; Mean In SEO?","options":["The Box With Paid Ads That Appear When You Perform A Search.","This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword","A Special Category Of Sites That Are Listed In Kid-safe Searches","The First 10 Search Results For A Particular Keyword."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"This Is Where Sites Are Kept Till They Get Mature Enough To Be Included In The Top Rankings For A Particular Keyword"},{"question":"# Q15. What Is Anchor Text?","options":["It Is The Main Body Of Text On A Particular Web Page","It Is The Text Within The Left Or Top Panel Of A Web Page","It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page","It Is The Most Prominent Text On The Page That The Search Engines Use To Assign A Title To The Page"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"It Is The Visible Text That Is Hyper Linked To Another Page"},{"question":"# Q16. Which Google search query should be used to return only PDF documents that reference Microsoft?","options":["Microsoft + .pdf","\"Microsoft\" + \"pdf\"","Microsoft AND \"pdf\"","Microsoft filetype:pdf"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Microsoft filetype:pdf"},{"question":"# Q17. Which link is not crawlable?","options":["<a href=\"http://domain.com\">","<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">","<a href=\"http://domain.com\" class=\"blue\">","<a href=\"../category-2/page\">"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"<a onclick=\"newwin('domain.com')\">"},{"question":"# Q18. Which choice represents the best header structure?\n- [ ]\n```markdown\nH1: How to Bak Bagels\nH2: Ingredients\nH3: Dry Ingredients\nH4: Wet Ingredients\nH2: Instructions\nH6: Reviews\n\n```","options":["- [ ]"]},{"question":"# Q19. All byline dates articles are suddenly no longer visible on a website's listing within Google Search. Assuming no changes have been made to the site programming or content, what is the most likely cause?","options":["The site has been delisted from Google Search","The site kept updating the date to make the content appear fresh, without changing the content.","The articles have aged more than 365 days without any significant updates to the content or the site.","A Google New sitemap was not provided within 30 days of setting up a Publisher Center account"]},{"question":"# Q20. What is an example of a Google search result that can be found in position zero?","options":["Google Ads result","featured snippet","related searches","autocomplete"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"featured snippet"},{"question":"# Q21. When creating accessible video content, what should you consider including?","options":["transcript","thumbnail","Flash Player","event tracking"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"transcript"},{"question":"# Q22. You are optimizing a website that sells supplies for banking donuts. Which approach is most appropriate to drive more organic traffic?","options":["Buy donutbakingsupplies.com and 301 redirect to your website","Add the keyword \"donut supplies\" to every page.","Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes","Join a link farm to rapidly build inbounnd links."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Create a new blog with high-quality donut recipes"},{"question":"# Q23. Why is it important to be mindful of outbound follow links?","options":["There is a limit to how many links you can create.","all of these answers","Any follow links reduce your PageRank by 1.","Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Your site's reputation is tied to the sites you link to."},{"question":"# Q24. Which statement is true about JSON-LD?","options":["It has no relation to JSON.","It is the only structured data format available.","It is considered the most complicated approach to adding structured data.","It is Google's preferred structured data format."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"It is Google's preferred structured data format."},{"question":"# Q25. What is a key reason why duplicate content might cause an issue with ranking?","options":["It creates an inability to use canonical URLs, which dramatically reduces crawl effectiveness,","It requires using a 302 redirect, which dilutes PageRank.","It triggers an immediate manual action penalty, which delists an entire domain until the duplicate content is removed.","It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"It makes it difficult for a search engine to determine the original and authoritative content source."},{"question":"# Q26. What attribute would you use to describe the content of an image?","options":["tabindex","longdesc","src","alt"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"alt"},{"question":"# Q27. You are researching keywords for a client and creating list for an optimization plan. Which is not a recommended method of creating keyword lists?","options":["synonyms and related words","queries about benefits, features, problems","how-to and question-based queries","focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"focusing on only high-volume, high-popularity words"},{"question":"# Q28. You want to get a rough idea of how many searches per month a particular search term gets. Which tool do you use?","options":["Google Keyword Planner","Google Tag Manager","Google Search Console","Google Suggest"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Google Keyword Planner"},{"question":"# Q29. Changing the title tag and/or meta description will have a measurable impact on your \\_\\_\\_\\_.","options":["RSS","CTR","PPC","LSI"]}]